sh
Bashar I'm interested in the
technology raw mentioned in the raw
material known as the prono vacuum how
can we
create
a PR
vacuum using today's
technology the so-called pra a vacuum is
the same thing as the idea of what you
might call the quantum vacuum is the
same thing as the Zero Point Energy
concept that many people are talking
about on your planet it exists all
around you the technology exists that
you can use to tap into it in certain
ways many of the kinds of things that
people have invented that say it's
tapping into the Zero Point Energy are
not exactly doing so but the idea is
growing in the Consciousness the
collective consciousness of your planet
until such time as that awareness
evolves into technology that will truly
tap into that pra field the quantum
field the void and whatever else you may
wish to call it it will allow you
unlimited energy unlimited flow an
inexhaustible supply of energy that can
be utilized in a variety of ways once
you truly tap into that technology it
has to do with creating devices of
proper resonance proper frequencies
capacitors that vibrate at certain
resonant frequencies that deliver and
transform energy in a certain way step
it down in a way that you can use with
your technology we have talked a little
bit about this as a space-time antenna
concept three nested spheres separated
by F ratio diameters penetrated by
antenna that are insulated from a merba
a double interpenetrated tetrahedron in
the center of the three spere
that resonates at certain frequencies
and can be activated by the introduction
of energy into it and it will output
energy of a higher caliber a higher
level and a higher frequency tapping
into the quantum field in certain ways
but many people on your planet a few of
them are beginning to experiment with
this and we cannot deliver more
information about this device until they
have already achieved what it is we have
already delivered end of
discussion hello Bashar good day uh
thank you for having this conversation
with each other in this way it is our
passion and our pleasure to do so what
would you like to discuss talking about
the hybrid children um you've mentioned
in the past that contact between hybrid
children and their mothers will expand
over time yes has this process indeed
started on this timeline is there is
there an increase of physical contact
between human beings and the hybrid
children yes but in an altered reality
not necessarily physically on your
planet so much but in a slightly altered
version of physical reality and in dream
time these encounters have increased
okay wonderful eventually it will leak
into the physical reality as you
understand it although it will still be
of a higher vibration than it is now yes
understand yeah and um I also wanted to
talk to you about suppressed memories
yes um during our previous conversation
you've mentioned
that I was visited by the grace when I
also was a child yes and that these
experiences are buried deep within my
Consciousness well not that deep oh not
that
deep you also mentioned that I felt
victimized because my childlike state
was not able to comprehend what was
going on during these visitations yes
okay and is it correct to say that from
the point of view as a human being child
that these visitations and the removal
of genetic material was somehow
experienced as a trauma on a
psychological
level yes but only because of the way
you were raised as a human not because
it's innate to the being a child not
because it's innate to being a human
child just because of the way your
planet views these kinds of things and
because it is shortsighted in its
compartmentalization of awareness that's
the only reason you experienced it
traumatically and is that also the
reason that we're still somehow afraid
of
extraterrestrials because you are afraid
of portions of your own power and the
extraterrestrials you're encountering
represent and reflect the idea of your
true power in certain
ways I understand and that yeah that's
probably not a coincidence but that
leads up to my next question um both my
parents have transitioned almost within
three years of each other and the last
parent my father passed one year ago yes
and their physical absence caused a
shift in my life yes of course that's
the purpose of it yeah um I experienced
this as a tremendous opportunity to shed
a whole bunch of negative belief systems
that I have bestowed upon myself through
their upbringing well congratulations
that is a positive way to use itk you
but I also sense that this tremendous
opportunity is sometimes a bit
frightening
why as if this whole new space that has
opened up is sometimes too big to handle
impossible otherwise you wouldn't
experience
it you only grow into the space you're
ready for so no matter how it looks
you're making a comparison still using
some of the outdated beliefs to view it
instead of letting go of those outdated
beliefs and understanding you cannot
experience more than you're ready for
anyway you can expand into it that's why
it looks that big because that's how big
you actually are when you let go of the
limiting
beliefs I understand what you're saying
I understand what you're saying and I
also um am aware of the physical impact
of this awareness yes uh uh for instance
when my body is sleeping yes it seems to
respond to this awareness with an actual
physical shock during the night that
eventually wakes me up
yes it can because again your body is
not used to that vibration or frequency
of energy but it can get used to it over
time and how how how can we do that can
you say something about um how to to
integrate this new space and the
awareness of new space and the physical
response to this is it just going with
the flow letting it happen that's one
way practice in a sense having it happen
over and over again you'll get used to
it that's one way but one way to
accelerate that is to understand or have
a
perspective where physical reality isn't
really separate from Spirit reality it's
really not so different it's just that
you've defined it as very different
you've plac certain definitions on
physical reality that makes it seem so
unlike Spirit reality when in fact it's
a natural extension of
it okay and the and the and the and the
physical body that's re acts um um how
can we smooth that out well this is what
I'm telling you stop making such a
separation in your belief system between
the idea of your physical body and your
spirit your physical body is your spirit
in physical terms it's the same kind of
idea if you wish a crude analogy of
saying ice is still water it's just
Frozen but it's the same thing it's the
same substance essentially and so is
steam so if you start looking at your
body as if it's simply euphemistically a
Frozen version of your spirit or at
least a portion of your spirit you can
start to allow the physical reality to
sort of melt a little bit more allow it
to become a little bit more fluid a
little bit more liquid and not be so
different from the liquid version or the
steam version
version so you have to start really
looking at physical reality as if it's
just another state of being of spirit
and not really separate it's the idea of
separation that's tripping you up yeah I
understand and
um you also said something about um that
the human beings on Earth will become
more and more human over time
yes you're actually not fully human yet
yeah and I was wondering what you meant
by that what does it mean to be human as
opposed to not being fully
human being fully human means that you
understand that everything is made of
unconditional love you understand that
everything is connected everything is a
reflection of everything else and you
act
accordingly yes being fully human is
what you ascribe to beings like Christ
Buddha Krishna so on and so forth It's
the idea of the behavior that reflects
the godhood within
you
yes yeah and that probably also means
that um we're not so
compartmentalized in our way of thinking
then exactly you think more holistically
more as a whole system that's why I said
you understand everything is one thing I
am you from another point of view
literally I am you from another point of
view you are us from another point of
view a fully realized human
lives in that truth yeah thank you so
much for sure you are so welcome a a
[Music]